Viewers all over the world, where can you go from His presence?
I can sense God's healing in your life.
I sense God touching you.
In the name of Jesus, be touched!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction - be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
That infirmity, wherever it is located, that disease, that sickness -
be healed, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being healed, touched!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Feel it.
Begin to feel it, right now.
I am feeling it, right now; I can sense it - you are healed!
I can sense it - you are delivered!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, right now, begin to bind your body.
The Bible says, "Whatever we bind here on earth shall be bound in Heaven.
Whatever we loose here on earth shall be loosed in Heaven".
Right now, begin to bind your body, soul, spirit to the will and purpose of God for your life,
in the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, command that demon who is behind that situation,
command them out!
Command that demon, spirit who is responsible for that situation,
who is responsible for that challenge, command that demon, command that devil,
command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You affliction - leave my people!
Viewers, wherever it is located, that disease, sickness, affliction, I command them out,
in the name of Jesus!
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction - leave my people!
You infirmity - leave my people!
You disease, sickness - I curse you, in the name of Jesus!
Loose, in the name of Jesus!
Confess your freedom, viewers all over the world!
Begin to confess your freedom.